

PROFILE

Professional with experience in different projects in the field of **data analytics** and **data science**.

During my experience and trainings, I acquired solid knowledge in technologies and tools such as Python, MySQL, Power Bi, in different libraries such as Numpy, Pandas, SciPy, Scikit-learn, Matplotlib, Seaborn, Plotly, Streamlit and Machine Learning techniques such as A/B testing, time series analysis and forecasting, supervised (Regression and Classification) and unsupervised learning.

In addition to my experience in data analysis, I also have a strong background in recruitment and people management. In previous roles i was responsible for recruiting IT profiles and managing the entire recruitment process, which gives me a great insight into the IT Industry.

SKILLS

- · Critical thinking.
- · Communication.
- · Complex problem solving.
- · Teamwork.
- · Proactivity.
- · Adaptability.
- \cdot Resilience.

COMPLEMENTARY TOOLS

- · Office environment, Excel avanced.
- · Agile metodologies, Scrum, Kanban.
- · Jira.

LANGUAGES

- · Spanish Native
- · English Fluent (B2)

CONTACT



javiergomezbiedma@gmail.com



+34 681 131 818

46970, Valencia, Spain



www.linkedin.com/in/javier-gomez-biedma



JAVIER GÓMEZ BIEDMA

Data Analyst/Data Scientist | Python | SQL | Power Bi

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

DATA ANALYSIS/DATA SCIENCE BOOTCAMP

UPGRADE HUB | MAY 2023 - AUG 2023

Technologies: Libraries: Machine learning: Python Numpy · A/B testing. · Visual Studio Code · Pandas · Time series analysis and · SciPv Jupyter Notebook prediction. · Google Colab · Scikit-learn · Supervised (Regression and · MySQL Matplotlib Classification) and · Power Bi · Seaborn unsupervised learning. · GitHub Plotly

· Streamlit

https://github.com/JGomez1100000

IT TALENT ACQUISITION

AMARIS CONSULTING | NOV 2022 - JUN 2023

- · Recruitment of IT profiles.
- · Publication of job offers in different sources.
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Reporting and monitoring of the area's KPIs.
- · Management of our own database.
- · Candidate search in different platforms (Boolean search).
- · Interviews and contact with candidates.

TALENT ACQUISITION / HR BUSINESS PARTNER

NORAUTO ESPAÑA | NOV 2021 - OCT 2022

RECRUITMENT AND PEOPLE MANAGEMENT

ANANDA ETT | DEC 2020 - MAR 2021

EDUCATION

DATA ANALYSIS/DATA SCIENCE BOOTCAMP

UPGRADE HUB | MAY 2023 - AUG 2023

GOOGLE DATA ANALYTICS PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATE

GOOGLE CAREER CERTIFICATES (COURSERA) | DEC 2022 - MAY 2023

- . > Sql
- > Big query
- > Tableau
- > R

MASTER'S DEGREE IN PEOPLE MANAGEMENT AND ORGANIZATIONAL GROWTH

ESIC BUSINESS & MARKETING SCHOOL | 2021-2022

DEGREE IN PSYCHOLOGY

UNIVERSIDAD JAUME I (CASTELLÓN) | 2016 - 2021

DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE (Not finished)

UNIVERSIDAD POLITÉCNICA DE VALENCIA | 2014 - 2016